http://www.taxslayer.com/policies/privacy

TaxSlayer's Privacy Policy
YOUR PRIVACY IS A PRIORITY TO US
At TaxSlayer.com (collectively 'We', 'Us', 'Our' or 'TaxSlayer'), we are committed to safeguarding customer information on our site www.taxslayer.com. Since your privacy is a priority to us, TaxSlayer will not share nonpublic information about you with third parties outside of the TaxSlayer corporate family without your consent, except as explained in our Privacy Policy. Moreover, we never sell your information, period.
Protecting your privacy is important to TaxSlayer. We want you to understand what information we may gather and how we may share it. This Privacy Policy explains TaxSlayer’s collection, use, retention and security of information about you. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. TaxSlayer is a U.S. based company offering products related to the preparation of U.S. federal and state tax returns. TaxSlayer does not market to nor target subjects of the European Union. Though GDPR does not apply, TaxSlayer meets and exceeds all rules and regulations relating to data protection and security promulgated by the Internal Revenue Service and its Security Summit (https://www.irs.gov/privacy-disclosure/security-summit for more information).
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We may collect your personal information as an individual for various purposes, such as the following:
Access and use of websites and online services
When entering one of our websites, or using an online service, we may record information necessary to provide you with access, for the operation of the website and for us to comply with security and legal requirements in relation to operating our site, such as usernames, passwords, IP addresses and browser settings. If you prepare and/or file a tax return using the Services on TaxSlayer.com, we collect additional information such as physical address, social security number, income, employment status, claimed deductions, and other information necessary to accurately complete your tax return. We also may collect information about your activities during your visit in order to personalize your website experience, such as recording your preferences and settings and to collect statistics to help us improve and further develop our websites, products, services, and appropriate offers
Responding to your request for information, order, or support
When you contact us (online or by phone or email) in connection with a request for information, help with ordering or paying for a product or service, or to provide you with assistance or support relating to your tax return preparation and filing, we collect information necessary to fulfill your request, to grant you access to the product or service, to provide you with support and to be able to contact you. For instance, we collect your name and contact information, details about your request, details about the services you have ordered or attempted to order, etc. As notified, we may record such information for administrative purposes, defending our rights, and in connection with our relationship with you.
Purchasing products or services
If you purchase our products or services, payment information such as credit card number and expiration date is collected to complete the transaction. Additional banking information such as account and routing numbers may be collected depending on whether a refund is anticipated or depending on the choice receipt of a refund.
Additional information collected
Most information we collect about you comes from our direct interactions with you. However, when you use our site, products, services, and apps, we may collect information regarding the type of device, system and performance information, operating system used, and mobile network information. Analytics software may record information such as how often you use the sites or application, the events that occur on the sites or within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the sites or application originated. Typically, we do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit on the sites or within the mobile app.
HOW AND WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION
In addition to the information you input directly, certain technologies such as: cookies, tags, or similar technologies are utilized by TaxSlayer and our partners affiliates, or analytics or service providers. As part of the information collected, we may record page views, mouse clicks, movements and scrolling activity. A device user may control the ability of access of some of these technologies at the individual browser level, however, this may disable or limit some of the features offered. The primary technologies used by TaxSlayer are: Adobe®, Hotjar®, Heap®, and Google®. For an updated and complete list of our providers please contact us at support@taxslayer.com.
We use the information collected to develop, improve, enhance, and secure our websites, products, and services. Specifically, the technologies listed above, and possibly others, are used in administering the websites and application, analyzing trends, evaluate functionality of our websites and application on your device, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these service providers on an individual as well as aggregated basis. Additionally, we use cookies for settings preferences, e.g., language preference. From time to time, we may send push notifications to update you about any alerts, offers, or promotions.
USE OF INFORMATION
Section 301-7216 of the Internal Revenue Code specifically governs the use and disclosure of Tax Return Information. Some states may also have additional laws and regulations related to use and disclosure of the same information. We use your Tax Return Information only in accordance with those applicable laws and regulations to prepare and assist in preparing your tax return, to provide services associated with preparing your tax return, and to provide you with other products and services you specifically request or consent to. We use the information you provide (discussed above) to complete purchases of products and services you request. As permitted by law, we may also use the information you provide to address questions submitted to our customer or technical support systems, to send updates or security alerts, marketing messages, or to provide notification of new products, services, enhancements, and promotions. We may use your information to show you relevant information and offer you other related products and services.
Lastly, we also use the information we collect to monitor and investigate fraud, identity theft, and other illegal activity and to personalize and improve our Services.
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
The privacy and security of your information is important to us. We do not sell or rent your information. As indicated below, we may share your information to support the products and services you request, or provide your information to third parties, upon your specific consent, for products and services that may benefit you.
We disclose Tax Return Information only in accordance with your requests, such as when filing a tax return with the IRS or state revenue authority. TaxSlayer may be required to preserve and disclose personal and Tax Return information, and any part thereof, without your consent as provided by law, such as, to respond to lawful requests by authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, a subpoena or court order, judicial process or bankruptcy proceedings, or regulatory authorities to protect against fraud and in compliance with the IRS Security Summit. Additionally, your information may be disclosed in connection with an actual sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or transfer of all or a portion of our business or relevant operating unit. We reserve the right to transfer your information as part of the transaction. In such an event, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership, incompatible new uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.
We may share information about you and the products and services you have purchased from us, to members of the TaxSlayer Corporate family and our parent company of Rhodes Financial Services all of whom follow our Privacy Policy. In some cases, your information may be disclosed to our service providers to complete a product purchase, to fulfill a service you request, or to market one of our products or services. While this may require us to share information, these service providers are strictly prohibited from using your information other than to act on our behalf.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION
TaxSlayer understands the importance of protecting customer information and we have a team dedicated to keeping your information secure. TaxSlayer meets and exceeds all rules and regulations relating to data protection and security for the tax industry promulgated by the Internal Revenue Service and its Security Summit (https://www.irs.gov/privacy-disclosure/security-summit for more information). TaxSlayer’s web-based and mobile applications secure information by utilizing a variety of security related technologies including, but not limited to, multi-factor authentication, firewalls, intrusion detection systems, encryption, access controls and alerts. TaxSlayer incorporates the use of SSL encryption facilitated by an Extended Validation SSL Certificate issued by a recognized trusted certificate authority to protect your sensitive data as it is entered into the system. We maintain Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance to ensure your payment information is safe. Additionally, our systems are routinely subject to automated vulnerability testing purposely exceeding the requirements of PCI compliance. This practice allows quicker identification and remediation of risks to the privacy of taxpayer data. Internal audits are performed continuously throughout the year to ensure compliance with regulatory standards and TaxSlayer’s Information Security Policy.
YOUR RIGHTS AND USER CONTROLS
You have control over your personal data and how it’s collected, used, and shared. Though TaxSlayer may be required to retain your Tax Return information for up to three tax years to comply with our legal obligations, you have the right to access any information held by TaxSlayer that you either input directly or information collected as described above.
Access to personal information
Upon request, TaxSlayer will provide you with certain personal information you specifically request by contacting customer support at support@taxslayer.com or via a request sent to our address provided below. Your information will be provided in a machine readable format. However, any tax returns will be available only in a non-fileable format.
Change or correct personal information
You may view, manage, delete and/or make changes to your personal information by visiting your account online at www.taxslayer.com and selecting “Edit Account Information” in the My Account dashboard. Or, by emailing our customer support at support@taxslayer.com or via mail at the contact information listed below.
Opt-out of technologies
You may choose to opt-out of certain technologies used on TaxSlayer’s website. However, the choice to opt-out of certain technologies may affect, alter, or eliminate the functionality of certain features of or the products and services offered by TaxSlayer. To review and access opt-out procedures for the primary technologies: Adobe®, Hotjar®, Heap®, and Google® click [here].
CONTACT US
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact customer support at support@taxslayer.com.
You can also write us at:
TaxSlayer.com Privacy
945 Broad St
Augusta, GA 30901
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
This Privacy Policy applies to products and services of TaxSlayer. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy and any of the policies described above, at any time. Any material changes to our policy will be immediately posted and made available to consumers on our website. Notification of changes may be made by email or by means of a notice on the Website.
Effective 11/15/2019
TaxSlayer Terms of Service
Please read the Terms of Service below. They cover the terms and conditions that apply to your use of this website (the "Website," or "Site"). TaxSlayer, LLC. ("TaxSlayer") may change the Terms of Service from time to time. By continuing to use the Site following such modifications, you agree to be bound by such modifications to the Terms of Service.
General Terms and Conditions. In consideration of use of the Site, you agree to: (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the registration page and (b) to maintain and update this information to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If any information provided by you is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, TaxSlayer has the right to terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of the Site. You agree not to resell or transfer the Site or use of or access to the Site.
You acknowledge and agree that you must: (a) provide for your own access to the World Wide Web and pay any service fees associated with such access, and (b) provide all equipment necessary for you to make such connection to the World Wide Web, including a computer and modem or other access device.
By using the TaxSlayer.com web site, including any applets, software, and content contained therein, you agree that use of the Site is entirely at your own risk. THE SITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTY FOR INFORMATION, DATA, SERVICES, UNINTERRUPTED ACCESS, OR PRODUCTS PROVIDED THROUGH OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE. SPECIFICALLY, TAXSLAYER DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO: (1) ANY WARRANTIES CONCERNING THE AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY, USEFULNESS, OR CONTENT OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AND (2) ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE, WARRANTY OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORTUOUS BEHAVIOR, NEGLIGENCE, OR UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION.
NEITHER TAXSLAYER NOR ANY OF ITS EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, AFFILIATES, WEBSITE CO-BRANDING PROVIDERS OR CONTENT OR SERVICE PROVIDERS SHALL BE LIABLE TO YOU OR OTHER THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF USE OF SERVICE OR INABILITY TO GAIN ACCESS TO OR USE THE SERVICE OR OUT OF ANY BREACH OF ANY WARRANTY. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE RESPECTIVE LIABILITY OF TAXSLAYER, ITS EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, AFFILIATES, WEBSITE CO-BRANDING PROVIDERS AND CONTENT OR SERVICE PROVIDERS RESPECTIVE LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY SUCH STATE LAW.
TaxSlayer is the owner and/or authorized user of any trademark, registered trademark and/or service mark appearing at this Web Site, and is the copyright owner or licensee of the content and/or information on this Website including but not limited to any screens appearing at the Site. You may not download and/or save a copy of any of the screens except as otherwise provided in these Terms of Service, for any purpose. However, you may print a copy of the information on this Site for your personal use or records. If you make other use of this Site, except as otherwise provided above, you may violate copyright and other laws of the United States, other countries, as well as applicable state laws and may be subject to penalties. TaxSlayer does not grant any license or other authorization to any user of its trademarks, registered trademarks, service marks, or other copyrightable material or other intellectual property, by placing them on this Website.
TaxSlayer reserves the right to change any information on this Website including but not limited to revising and/or deleting features or other information without prior notice. Clicking on certain links within this Website might take you to other web sites for which TaxSlayer assumes no responsibility of any kind for the content, availability or otherwise. (See "Links from and to this Website" below.) The content presented at this Site may vary depending upon your browser limitations.
User Conduct On the Site.
While using the Site, you may not:
restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Site; or
post or transmit any unlawful, fraudulent, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, profane, threatening, abusive, hateful, offensive, or otherwise objectionable information of any kind, including without limitation any transmissions constituting or encouraging conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any local, state, national or foreign law, including without limitation the U.S. export control laws and regulations; or
post or transmit any advertisements, solicitations, chain letters, pyramid schemes, investment opportunities or schemes or other unsolicited commercial communication (except as otherwise expressly permitted by TaxSlayer) or engage in spamming or flooding; or
post or transmit any information or software which contains a virus, trojan horse, worm or other harmful component; or
post, publish, transmit, reproduce, distribute or in any way exploit any information, software or other material obtained through the Site for commercial purposes (other than as expressly permitted by the provider of such information, software or other material); or
upload, post, publish, transmit, reproduce, or distribute in any way, information, software or other material obtained through the Site which is protected by copyright, or other proprietary right, or derivative works with respect thereto, without obtaining permission of the copyright owner or rightholder; or
upload, post, publish, reproduce, transmit or distribute in any way any component of the Site itself or derivative works with respect thereto, as the Site is copyrighted as a collective work under U.S. copyright laws.
TaxSlayer has no obligation to monitor the Site. However, you acknowledge and agree that TaxSlayer has the right to monitor the Site electronically from time to time and to disclose any information as necessary or appropriate to satisfy any law, regulation or other governmental request, to operate the Site properly, or to protect itself or its customers. TaxSlayer will not intentionally monitor or disclose any private electronic-mail message unless required by law. TaxSlayer reserves the right to refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, that, in its sole discretion, are unacceptable, undesirable, inappropriate or in violation of these Terms of Service.
Unless otherwise indicated for a particular communication, any communications or material of any kind that you e-mail, post or otherwise transmit through this Website, including data, questions, comments or suggestions ("your Communications") will be treated as non-confidential and nonproprietary. In addition, TaxSlayer is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in your Communications for any purpose including, but not limited to, developing and marketing products using such information without compensation to you.
Failure to Comply With Terms and Conditions and Termination. You acknowledge and agree that TaxSlayer may terminate your password or account or deny you access to all or part of the Site without prior notice if you engage in any conduct or activities that TaxSlayer in its sole discretion believes violate any of the terms and conditions, violate the rights of TaxSlayer, or is otherwise inappropriate for continued access.
You acknowledge and agree that TaxSlayer may in its sole discretion deny you access through TaxSlayer to any materials stored on the Internet, or to access third party services, merchandise or information on the Internet through TaxSlayer, and TaxSlayer shall have no responsibility to notify any third-party providers of services, merchandise or information nor any responsibility for any consequences resulting from lack of notification.
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold TaxSlayer and its affiliates harmless from any and all claims, liabilities, costs and expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees, arising in any way from your use of the Site or the placement or transmission of any message, information, software or other materials through the Site by you or users of your account or related to any violation of these Terms of Service by you or users of your account.
Links from and to this Website. You acknowledge and agree that TaxSlayer and any of its website co-branding providers have no responsibility for the accuracy or availability of information provided by linked sites. Links to external web sites do not constitute an endorsement by TaxSlayer or its website co-branding providers of the sponsors of such sites or the content, products, advertising or other materials presented on such sites.
Information in the many web pages that are linked to TaxSlayer's Website comes from a variety of sources. Some of this information comes from official TaxSlayer licensees, but much of it comes from unofficial or unaffiliated organizations and individuals, both internal and external to TaxSlayer. TaxSlayer does not author, edit, or monitor these unofficial pages or links. You acknowledge and agree that TaxSlayer and its Website Co-branding Providers shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on such external sites or resources.
Other Information. TaxSlayer is taking reasonable and appropriate measures, including encryption, to ensure that your personal information is disclosed only to those specified by you. However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot and do not guarantee that the personal information you have entered will not be intercepted by others and decrypted.
If you wish to make purchases through the Site, you may be asked by the merchant or information or service provider from whom you are making the purchase to supply certain information, including credit card or other payment mechanism information. You agree not to hold TaxSlayer liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as a result of any such dealings with any merchant or information or service provider through the Site. You agree that all information you provide any merchant or information or service provider through the Site for purposes of making purchases will be accurate, complete and current. The merchants and information and service providers offering merchandise, information and services through the Site set their own prices and may change prices or institute new prices at any time. You agree to pay all charges incurred by users of your account and credit card or other payment mechanism at the prices in effect when such charges are incurred. You also will be responsible for paying any applicable taxes relating to purchases through the Site.
IRS Circular 230 Notice. Nothing in our communications with you (including, but not limited to, any emails, web site content, attachments, enclosures or other accompanying materials) relating to any federal tax transaction or matter are considered to be "covered opinions" as described in Circular 230.
Miscellaneous. The Terms of Service and the relationship between you and TaxSlayer shall be governed by the laws of the State of Georgia without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You and TaxSlayer agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within the state of Georgia.
The failure of TaxSlayer to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Terms of Service shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of the Terms of Service is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties' intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of the Terms of Service remain in full force and effect.
Pricing. By using this site you acknowledge and agree that TaxSlayer provides listing prices only as a guide. Pricing is determined at the time or print/e-file and is subject to change at any time without prior notice.
*
Classic and Premium packages include all available online IRS forms.
Pricing based upon customer service selections. "Everything" refers to all applicable IRS forms and schedules and the preparation of a federal tax return.
All prices here, and on all outward facing TaxSlayer.com sites, are subject to change at any time without notice. Price is determined at the time of print and/or e-file. Published prices are meant only as a guide and are not a guarantee.
TaxSlayer.com will not display correctly in Internet Explorer 7.
Please upgrade your browser before proceeding:
-or-
Download the TaxSlayer Go App on IOS & Android devices.
Prepare and E-File Your State Tax Return for $39
TaxSlayer makes it easy to prepare and e-file your state taxes.
We’ll transfer your information automatically from your federal tax return to your state return, so you don’t have to.
TaxSlayer State Return
You pay: $39 per state
Each additional state tax return is $39. Actual prices are determined at the time of print or e-file. Offer is subject to change or end without notice.
Prepare and E-File Your State Tax Return for Free
TaxSlayer makes it easy to prepare and e-file your state taxes. We’ll transfer your information automatically from your federal tax return to your state return, so you don’t have to.
TaxSlayer Simply Free
$0 for state* | $0 for federal
*TaxSlayer Simply Free includes one free state tax return. Each additional state tax return is $39. Actual prices are determined at the time of print or e-file. Offer is subject to change or end without notice.
Prepare and E-File Your State Tax Return for $39
TaxSlayer makes it easy to prepare and e-file your state taxes.
We’ll transfer your information automatically from your federal tax return to your state return, so you don’t have to.
TaxSlayer Self-Employed
You pay: $39 per state
Each additional state tax return is $39. Actual prices are determined at the time of print or e-file. Offer is subject to change or end without notice.
TaxSlayer Self-Employed
TaxSlayer Self-Employed is the perfect solution for taxpayers who are self-employed or do freelance work.
TaxSlayer Self-Employed includes the following features:
PreSDDSpare, E-file, and Print
State Return Included
Free Email Support
Live Phone Support
Deduction Finder
All Major Forms
PDF Import
Fast W-2 Import
TaxSlayer Premium
TaxSlayer Premium is the perfect solution for taxpayers who are self-employed or do freelance work.
TaxSlayer Self-Employed includes the following features:
Prepare, E-file, and Print
Free Email Support
Live Phone Support
Deduction Finder
All Major Forms
PDF Import
Fast W-2 Import
Pull Prior Year Info
TaxSlayer Classic
TaxSlayer Classic supportrs all major forms and can import your W-2.
TaxSlayer Classic includes the following features:
Prepare, E-file, and Print
Free Email Support
Live Phone Support
Deduction Finder
All Major Forms
PDF Import
Fast W-2 Import
Pull Prior Year Info
Federal Return + State Return
TaxSlayer Simply Free is the perfect solution for taxpayers who have simple tax returns
Prepare, E-file, and Print
State Return Included
Free Email Support
Live Phone Support
Deduction Finder
PDF Import
Prepare, E-file, and Print
State Return Included
Free Email Support
Live Phone Support
Deduction Finder
PDF Import
TaxSlayer is proud to offer qualified customers with a completely Free Federal tax return. Available to all U.S. residents and resident aliens with an AGI $69,000 or less and age 51 or younger.
File a free state return if you qualify for our free federal offer and you are filing one of the following states:
AR, AZ, DC, GA, IA, ID, IN, KY, MA, MI, MN, MO, MS, MT, NC, ND, NY, OR, RI, SC, VA, VT, WV.
For those who do not qualify the price to file a federal tax return is $17 and the state is $39.
TaxSlayer se enorgullece de ofrecer a los clientes calificados una declaración de impuestos federal completamente gratuita. Disponible para todos los residentes de los EE. UU. Y extranjeros residentes con un AGI de $69,000 o menos y de 51 años o menos.
Presente una declaración estatal gratuita si califica para nuestra oferta federal gratuita y está presentando uno de los siguientes estados:
AR, AZ, DC, GA, IA, ID, IN, KY, MA, MI, MN, MO, MS, MT, NC, ND, NY, OR, RI, SC, VA, VT, WV.
Para aquellos que no califican, el precio para presentar una declaración de impuestos federales es de $17 y el estado es de $39.
TaxSlayer is proud to offer qualified customers with a completely Free Federal tax return. Available to all U.S. residents and resident aliens with an AGI $69,000 or less and age 51 or younger.
File a free state return if you qualify for our free federal offer and you are filing one of the following states:
AR, AZ, DC, GA, IA, ID, IN, KY, MA, MI, MN, MO, MS, MT, NC, ND, NY, OR, RI, SC, VA, VT, WV.
For those who do not qualify the price to file a federal tax return is $17 and the state is $39.
Guaranteed Maximum Refund
We guarantee you will receive the maximum refund you are entitled or we will refund you the applicable TaxSlayer purchase price paid.
If you get a larger refund or smaller tax amount due from another tax preparation engine with the same data, we will refund the applicable purchase price you paid to TaxSlayer.com. Our Simply Free Edition is excluded from this guarantee. To qualify for the guarantee, the larger refund or smaller tax due cannot be attributed to variations in data you provided TaxSlayer for tax preparation, or for positions taken by you or your preparer that are contrary to the law. Furthermore, our Maximum Refund Guarantee is based on the schedules and forms supported by TaxSlayer. Click here to learn how to notify TaxSlayer if you believe you are entitled to a refund.
Reembolso Máximo Garantizado
Le garantizamos que recibirá el reembolso máximo que le corresponde o le reembolsaremos el precio de compra de TaxSlayer correspondiente pagado.
Si obtiene un reembolso mayor o un monto de impuestos más pequeño debido de otro motor de preparación de impuestos con los mismos datos, le reembolsaremos el precio de compra aplicable que pagó a TaxSlayer.com. Nuestra edición Simply Free está excluida de esta garantía. Para calificar para la garantía, el reembolso más grande o el impuesto más pequeño adeudado no se pueden atribuir a las variaciones en los datos que proporcionó a TaxSlayer para la preparación de impuestos, o para posiciones tomadas por usted o su preparador que sean contrarias a la ley. Además, nuestra Garantía de reembolso máximo se basa en los programas y formularios admitidos por TaxSlayer. Haga clic aquí para obtener información sobre cómo notificar a TaxSlayer si cree que tiene derecho a un reembolso.
Thank you for sharing!
Follow TaxSlayer Online:
Zero Out of Pocket Fees
We offer you the option to deduct your TaxSlayer filing fees
directly from your federal tax refund.
This option allows you to file your federal return and state return(s) electronically, and to have your refunds directly deposited into your personal checking or savings account with NO OUT OF POCKET EXPENSE. This option usually takes 10-18 days to complete. This option requires you to provide a valid phone number, email address and bank account information in your return. This is a good choice for those with a checking or savings account who do not want to pay any OUT OF POCKET EXPENSES. This option is the same as a Direct Deposit, except that TaxSlayer filing fees are deducted from your federal refund. To use this option you must be filing a Federal return and receiving a refund from your federal return to cover the expenses listed above.
1.	TaxSlayer is a registered trademark of TaxSlayer LLC, H&R Block® is a registered trademark of HRB Innovations®, Inc. TurboTax® and Quicken® are registered trademarks of Intuit®, Inc. TaxAct® is a registered trademark of TaxAct®, Inc.
2.	Prices based on http://www.hrblock.com/financial-services/tax-refund-payment/ , https://turbotax.intuit.com/ (Important offers details and disclosures/ Pay for Turbo Tax out of your refund) and http://www.taxact.com/tsupport/FAQDisplay.aspx (Prices confirmed with TaxAct support team on January 12, 2015 at 11:05 AM).
Terms and conditions apply.
3.	TaxSlayer is not affiliated with H&R Block®, TurboTax®, and TaxAct®.
100% Accurate Calculations
Double-check your entries to be sure you entered all of your information correctly. Next, we'll check your return for errors (based on the data you entered). This ensures your return is processed by the IRS and state(s) without delay. We stand behind our always up-to-date calculations and guarantee 100% accuracy, or we will reimburse you any federal or state penalties and interest charges. You are responsible for paying any additional tax owed.
TaxSlayer guarantees 100% accurate calculations or we will reimburse you any federal and/or state penalties and interest charges.
Cálculos 100% precisos
Antes de que presente su declaración electrónica, verificamos si hay errores y datos faltantes en su declaración para garantizar que el IRS la procese sin demora.
TaxSlayer garantiza cálculos precisos al 100% o le reembolsaremos cualquier multa federal o estatal y los cargos por intereses
Prepare and E-file a State Tax Return
TaxSlayer makes it easy to prepare and e-file your state return.
We will automatically transfer information from your federal tax return to your state tax return.
TaxSlayer Military Edition:
$39 for first state return
Each additional state tax return is $39. Actual prices are determined at the time of print or e-file and
are subject to change without notice.
Offer may change or end at any time without notice.
Ask a Tax Professional
You’ve got questions. We’ve got answers. On-staff IRS-enrolled agents and tax preparers will work on a solution to your problem so that you can focus on what’s important: a quick and accurate tax return.
Major Forms and Schedules Supported
To see the complete list of major forms and schedules supported by TaxSlayer, visit the *Supported Federal Forms page. The items listed here will be used to complete your return.
Audit Assistance
You want to safeguard your tax return, just in case. In the event of an IRS audit, TaxSlayer will help you resolve the matter as quickly as possible.
Free email & phone support
Stuck on your tax return and need technical advice within the program? That’s no problem with our complimentary email and live phone support! A professional support agent will assist you in finding a solution to your question.
Please check the contact us link in your my account for the support center hours of operation. Usually, email responses can be expected within 24 to 48 hours.
Prior Year Comparisons
You want all your tax documents on hand, in one place. Import your W-2s and PDFs from another online tax service or tax preparer. Existing TaxSlayer customers can pull prior year tax information and compare this year’s tax return with last year’s tax return.
Priority support
You want help—now. Jump to the front of the line with priority support via email, live chat, or phone.
Get All The Tax Help You Could Need With Our Live Phone and Email Support
TaxSlayer.com Classic includes Live Phone Support. In addition, you can contact TaxSlayer Support specialists by email about any questions you may have. TaxSlayer.com’s Knowledge Center also provides you with valuable tax knowledge and troubleshooting tips. Select the Learn More links or the Helpful Page topics for on screen assistance. You can also enter key words to search additional articles.
